Southern New England Telephone Company Records
© 2005 University of Connecticut
- Series X: Audio/Visual, undated, 1951-1998
  - 16 Millimeter Sound On Film, (3 inch reels)
    - Commercials
      - Business Commercials, 1980
      - Business Phone (2), 1974 April
      - Business Phone “Emergency”, undated
      - Business Telephone (5), 1973
      - Business Telephone (2), undated (Box 375)
      - Car (2), 1974 March
      - Categories (8), undated, 1966
      - Chinese Restaurant (2), undated
      - Chinese Restaurant (2), undated (Box 376)
      - Chocolates (2), undated
      - Chocolates and China (2), undated
      - Christmas, undated
      - Christmas Elf (2), 1974 November
      - Christmas Gift Phones (5), undated, 1964 November
      - Christmas Teenager, undated (Box 377)
      - Confederate General (2), undated
      - Contest (2), [1968?], undated
      - Convenience (2), 1973 April
      - Decotel (4), 1973 April, undated
      - Decotel Christmas (2), 1972 December
      - Deco-Tel, 1972 September
      - Deco-Tel, 1972 September (Box 378)
      - Decotel Phones, 1972 September
      - Decorator Telephone (2), undated
      - Do It Yourself (3), 1973 April
      - Egg Timer (2), 1975 February
      - Extension Phones, 1976 March
      - Energy and Energy Building, undated
      - Family (3), 1976 February
      - Farewell (2), undated (Box 379)
      - Faucet, 1976 March
      - Football (4), undated
      - Gangster (4), undated
      - Gambler (2), undated
      - Gift Certificate, undated
      - Gift Ideas (2), 1974 November (Box 380)
      - Home Phone Decorating (12), undated
      - Home Phone Decorating (2), undated (Box 381)
      - I Like That (4), 1975 December
      - Installer (4), 1971 July
      - J Monday's Child, 1969 January
      - Joe College (3), 1971 July
      - Joe College, undated (Box 382)
      - Kids (6), undated
      - Kitchen (3), [1966?]
      - Laundry, undated
      - Living Book (2), undated
      - Living Room, [1966?]
      - Locksmith (4), undated (Box 383)
      - Martian, 1967 June
      - Mickey, 1979 May
      - Mother's Day (4), 1973 May
      - Motorcycle (4), undated, 1966 January
      - Motorcycle (2), 1965 (Box 384)
      - My Sister The Doctor, undated
      - Niagara (4), undated
      - Operator (6), 1971 July
      - Party, undated
      - Party (3), undated (Box 385)
      - Patches, 1978
      - Pepper (2), [1968?]
      - Popcorn Eaters (3), undated
      - Porch and Patio (2), 1975 August
      - Phone Ranger (3), undated
      - Phone Ranger, undated (Box 386)
      - Phone Store, 1968 February
      - Pitchman, [1968?]
      - Racer (2), undated
      - Rain (2), undated
      - Santa (2), 1970 November
      - Santa Claus, 1968
      - Santa Claus/Phone Store, undated
      - Santa's Workshop, Teenage Times, Trimline Phone, 1974
      - Santa's Workshop, 1968 November
      - Schuster Express, undated
      - Schuster Express, 1974 (Box 387)
      - Sculptures, 1979 May
      - Simple Act (5), 1975 July
      - Simply Beautiful, undated
      - Singing Lineman, undated
      - Skateboard (5), undated, 1965 October
      - Sleigh Ride (2), 1971 November (Box 388)
      - Sports Store (2), 1973 January
      - Squares (2), 1973 April
      - Strike (SNET) (5), undated
      - Styles and Colors (2), undated
      - Styles and Colors (5), 1973-1974 (Box 389)
      - Swimmer (2), undated
      - Teenager (5), 1966 December
      - Telephone Products (2), 1972 February
      - Tree (2), undated (Box 390)
      - Tree-Candlestick (2), 1976 December
      - Trimline (7), 1967, 1974
      - Truck Repair, undated
      - Vignettes, undated
      - Window, 1974 May
      - Window, 1974 March (Box 391)
      - Window Washer, 1977 May
      - Workshop and Tree, 1975
      - World On A String, 1972 March
      - Worn Out, undated
      - Yellow Pages, 1968 August
      - Yellow Pages
        - Bakery, 1974 March
        - Business, 1965
        - Chocolate, [1968?]
        - Kids (2), undated
        - Locksmith, undated
        - Pants, Dog, Glasses, 1977 August
        - Waterbury Welding, 1965 (Box 392)
      - 411 Information, 1968 December
      - 113A Data Phone, undated
      - 1936 Musical (3), 1970 February
      - 1940 Army (3), [1970?]
  - 16 millimeter sound on film, (5 inch reels)
    - Commercials
      - Long Distance, 1971 (Box 393)
      - New Extensions, [1960s?]
      - The World On A String, undated
      - We Hear You, undated
      - Yellow Pages
        - Square, Ignition, Window, Bakery, Sports Store, 1974
  - Microfilm 35 millimeter (arranged by SNET reel #)
    [gaps-dates = when microfilmed]
    - Executive/Financial Department
      - Memorandum of Instrument (Box 394)
        - P0055, 1951 October
        - P0056, 1951 October
        - P0057, 1951 October
        - P0058, 1951 October
        - P0059, 1951 November
        - P0060, 1951 November
        - P0061, 1951 November
        - P0062, 1951 November (Box 395)
      - Contracts
        - P0063, 1951 November
        - P0064, 1951 November
        - P0065, 1951 November
        - P0066, 1951 November
      - Deeds
        - P0067, 1951 November
        - P0068, 1951 November
      - Minutes P0069, 1951 August (Box 396)
      - Financial P0072, 1952 August
      - General Cash Book P0073, 1952 September
      - Financial P0074, 1953 May
      - Memo of Instrument P0075, 1953 May
      - Financial P0076, 1953 August
      - Memo of Instrument P0077, 1953 August
      - Notes P0078, 1954 February (Box 397)
      - Card Record (Woodbury) P0079, 1954 April
      - Stock Shares P0080, 1954 December
      - Financial P0081, 1955 April
      - Financial P0082, 1955 July
      - Bonds P0083, 1956 July
      - Memo of Instrument P0084, 1956 July
      - Financial P0085, 1957 May (Box 398)
      - Contracts, Minutes P0086, 1957 May
      - Bonds P0087, 1957 May
      - Bank Register P0122, 1959 April
      - Stockholder Minutes P0123, 1959 April
      - Company Contracts P0125, 1959 April
      - Bonds P0131, 1961 November
      - Memo of Instrument P0132, 1961 November (Box 399)
      - Memo of Instrument P0135, 1961 January
      - Financial P0136, 1962 October
      - Financial P0137, 1963 March
      - Leases and Deeds P0138, 1963 March
      - Deeds P0139, 1963 March
      - Deeds P0140, 1963 March
      - Deeds, Contracts P0141, 1963 April (Box 400)
      - Contracts P00142, 1963 April
      - Minutes P0143, 1963 April
  - Microfilm 16 millimeter
    - Executive/Financial Department
      - Minutes P0025, 1966 January
      - Contracts P0046, 1967 March
      - Engineering, Grants P0048, 1967 April
      - Accounting P0060, 1968 October
      - Warrant Usage
        - 0063, 1968 October
        - 0064, 1968 October
        - 0065, 1968 October
        - 0066, 1968 October
      - Active Contracts 0071, 1951 November (Box 401)
      - Warrant Usage 0073, 1968 November
      - Budgets 0078, 1970
      - Bonds, Memo of Instrument P0144, 1963 December
      - Memo of Instrument P0145, 1963 December
      - Stockholder Record Card P0149, 1964 April
      - Contracts P0226, 1969 September
      - Accounting, Minutes P0231, 1969
      - Contracts, Leases P0244, 1969-1970
      - Vital Records P0281, 1973 June
      - Vital Records, Contracts, State Projects P0306-307, 1974 June
      - Vital Records P0307-312, 1974 June
      - Vital Records, Minutes P0313, undated
      - Vital Records P0354 (1 of 2), 1974-1975
      - P0354 (2 of 2), 1974-1975 (Box 402)
      - Contracts P0427, 1970-1976
      - Projects, Contracts, Minutes P0431 (1 of 3), 1975-1976
      - P0431 (2 of 3), 1975-1976
      - P0431 (3 of 3), 1975-1976
      - Debenture List P0434 (1 of 3), 1976 June
      - P0434 (2 of 3), 1976 June
      - P0434 (3 of 3), 1976 June
      - Com Key Equipment Contracts P0449 (1 of 2), 1975-1976
      - P0449 (2 of 2), 1976-1983
      - Minutes P0452, 1970-1972
      - Com Key Equipment Contracts P7700 (1 of 2), 1976-1977
      - P7700 (2 of 2), 1976-1977
      - Contracts, Leases, Deeds P7751 (1 of 2), 1976-1977
      - P7751 (2 of 2), 1976-1977 (Box 403)
      - Minutes P7752, 1976-1977
      - Com Key Contracts P7761, 1977
      - Com Key Contracts P7801, 1978
      - Contracts, Leases, Deeds, Legal Minutes P7816 (1 of 2), 1977-1978
      - P7816 (2 of 2), 1977-1978
      - Com Key Contracts P7824, 1978
      - Contracts, Leases, Deeds P7825, 1978
      - Com Key Contracts P7902, 1979 January - July
      - Contracts, Leases, Deeds P7903, 1979 January - July
      - Contracts, Agreements P7940, 1974-1979
      - Com Key Contracts P7954, 1979 August - December
      - Contracts, Leases, Deeds P7955, 1979-1980 January
      - Minutes P8029, 1978-1980
  - Return to SNET Records.